teapplix.com 2013-10-23

# Privacy Policy | Teapplix

This privacy statement discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it and how to correct or change it.

## Collection of Information

### What personal information we collect

Teapplix collects personally identifiable information when you register on our site. The information collected may include any of the following: email, name, IP address, browser information, address, billing address. Any comments or questions you submit are recorded as well. When entering Teapplix’s site, information may be collected about previous sites the person has viewed. 

### How we use the information collected

The goal of collecting customer and viewer information is to create a friendlier, smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while working with Teapplix. Personal information submitted at the time of registration may be used by Teapplix for the marketing and promotion of Teapplix products that we feel may be of interest to you.

### We do not disclose your information to thirdparties

We take your privacy seriously. Teapplix will not share your information with thirdparties. 

### Other information

By submitting personal information to us or using our site, you agree that we may collect and use such personal information in accordance with our privacy policy or as permitted by law. If you do not agree with these terms, do not provide any personal information to us. If you refuse or withdraw consent, or do not provide us with any necessary personal information, we may not be able to provide you with service. 

### Removal from our Database

To request removal from the database, simply [contact us](http://www.teapplix.com/contact.html) and we will be happy to remove your information immediately. Every email sent to you from Teapplix will also include a link to remove your email address from the mail server. If you request that we modify or remove all of your personal information, we will promptly do so, to the extent possible. Once your personal information has been removed you will not be able to use our services unless you re-register. 

### Changing of personal information

You may edit your personal information at any time by clicking on the "My Account" tab when you are signed in to Teapplix. All information may be changed including: address, credit card information, billing address, email and more. The new information will be updated in our system and used in the collection of information when visiting Teapplix. 

### Questions, comments, concerns

All questions, comments and concerns can be submitted via the [contact us form](http://www.teapplix.com/contact.html). You will receive an answer as soon as possible.
